Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Nah. nah.
nah. nah. nah.
Yo. too damn sloppy on the heel
stand to hop. shuffle. ball
change.
Here we go.
A two. a one. two. three. four.
♪ This is that new shá*áá*á
Keep tearing ya mind ♪
♪ That Universal Mind Control
Now move your behind ♪
♪ You know you like it
It's calling your name ♪
What do you think?
Too much for my first day?
Not enough.
Huh?
Yup. Always on the
same page. I like that.
Okay. what do you think? Huh?
You're pleased?
Great. As long as you are happy.
Let's do it. Huh? Yeah.
You're my best
advocate--
Am I in a dream?
- Chocolate chip pancakes.
Eggs à la Elliot.
- Oh? Which are what exactly?
- Scrambled eggs.
Sausage pucks.
- Uh-huh?
- Freshly brewed cup of coffee.
And a squeezed forever ago OJ.
You guys. I don't even know what
to say. You're the best.
We wanted you to be ready for
your first official day doing...
What exactly are you doing?
Helping the cops solve cases.
Do you get your own squad car?
No. but I will be making enough
money that we can get our actual
car back.
You know. speaking of more
money. we should talk IRAs at
some point soon.
SIMPLE. SEP and Roth.
Uh. yeah.
Let's not get ahead of
ourselves.
The point is this job. you guys.
if I don't quit or get fired.
is gonna help us
out. In lots of ways.
Uh.
Okay. gotta run. Thank
you so much again.
- Don't eat those.
- Wasn't planning on it.
Good morning.
Dad!
You are just in time. And good
news. she's a barfer today.
Oh. barfy baby. I got her.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Now that the LAPD is
paying me to manny.
I love you!
- Bye. Mom. Love you.
- Love you.
Samson. you busting out the
monk straps? -
What the heck? Who's
the lucky lady?
She's a florist. Loves
chess. lives close.
You dog.
I better be invited
to that wedding.
Let's hope.
Aren't you our cleaning lady?
Not today. Check back in with me
tomorrow after we see how this
goes.
We're really doing this. huh?
We're doing it.
Damien Ross.
Fell three stories onto his car.
911 got an anonymous call
from someone who heard the
impact.
EMTs rushed him
to County General.
He's in surgery now.
not sure if he'll make it.
At first blush.
I'm thinking suicide attempt.
Strange as it may sound.
Damien was found wearing tap
shoes.
so maybe he jumped
after one last dance.
- Mmm.
-"Mmm" what?
Oh.
No. nothing. Just...
I mean... You know.
No. I don't know.
Morgan. if this is gonna work.
and I can't believe
I'm actually saying this.
you have to say what
you're thinking.
Okay. I think we need to get up
on that roof.
Okay. See how easy that was?
Okay. so... Let it rip.
"Let it rip"?
I thought you were gonna hit me
with a bunch of obscure
scientific
or historical details about
rooftops or something.
Okay. well. "lay it on me"
would work there.
Okay.
Was anything attached to this
when you guys first got here?
No. the techs haven't been up
here yet. so we're first to the
scene.
Okay.
Morgan.
- What?
Gloves. please.
Yes. gloves.
How could I forget the gloves?
So. if something were attached
to this tripod
and it got knocked
over. it would be...
Huh.
Looks like you found Damien's
phone. -Hmm.
"Hmm"?
I don't know if
this was Damien's.
So. you think someone else was
up here with him?
Well. I certainly don't think
he was up here dancing by
himself.
Whoever's phone this is was left
- handed based on the smudge
patterns.
We'll dust for prints.
I don't know who
this little guy is.
Oh. De Perros de Tijuana.
Mexican baseball team.
They won the title a few years
back.
Hey. so you're
good for the obscure sports
references.
Got it. What are you doing?
- Turning on the phone. Morgan.
- I can turn the phone on.
I'm sure you can.
It is possible that Damien
was a left-handed baseball fan.
you know.
Oh!
Michelangelo's 1487 painting.
The Torment of Saint Anthony.
It's a glorious depiction
of the struggle suffered
by the patron saint
of lost things.
Well. maybe Damien
was a Catholic.
Until we know for certain
that this phone is--
You know. Karadec. normally I
drive a 1970 Oldsmobile Vista
Cruiser.
It's in the shop right now.
but I love that car.
I love it so much it loves me.
We take good care of each other.
It's probably the healthiest
relationship I've ever had.
Here's my point:
Damien loved his car.
He was obsessed with it.
If he was trying to
take his own life.
I am not buying for a second
that he would take his beloved
'81 Cutlass with him.
And you may very well be right.
Morgan. but that's still just a
theory. I need--
Evidence! You need your
evidence. You love your
evidence. I'm learning that.
Have you ever seen
tap dancing live?
It's captivating.
Here's what I think:
Damien was up here dancing
under the stars.
fully immersed in the
intoxicating art of
improvisation that is tap.
when someone pushed
him over the edge.
So I just checked in with CSI to
see if Damien had his cell phone
on him
when he arrived at the hospital.
And?
He did.
This phone belongs to someone
else.
So now we pray to Saint Anthony
that he helps us find
whoever pushed Damien off this
roof.
Daphne. I need an
update on Damien.
On hold. County
General. Stand by.
Oz. talk to me.
Fast-tracking CSI evidence
from Damien's car.
Good. Karadec and Morgan are in
transit with the suspect's
phone.
I want it processed
within the hour.
Selena.
Lieutenant Melon.
to what do I owe the pleasure?
You feeling generous today?
I need an extra pair of hands
in Robbery-Homicide.
Well. it's your lucky day
because we're just hanging
around here in Major Crimes
with a whole lot
of nothing to do.
This is serious.
Six jewelry stores hit
in the last two months.
I'm getting hammered in the
press. Cap's all over me.
I'm even catching heat
from my girlfriend.
'cause she's too scared to go
shop for an engagement ring.
Aren't you supposed to shop
for the engagement ring?
I need to catch this guy
before someone gets hurt or
killed.
You know I wouldn't ask
if I didn't really need the
assist.
'Cause if there was a scuffle on
the roof we can assume our
suspect's gonna have--
Have scratches. I get it.
Well. not just scratches.
I mean. based on this photo. look.
That's an ass pattern.
An ass pattern.
Yeah.
Listen. I've fallen
a lot in my life.
and trust me. whoever made those
marks has lacerations all over
the buns
and likely a bruised
coccyx. Tailbone.
I know what a coccyx is.
Daphne. what's the latest on
Damien? -Still on hold.
Hey. Melon alert.
Oh.
"Melon alert"?
All right. listen up.
Teamwork makes the dream work.
And right now. our friends
in Robbery need our help.
Beggars can't be
choosers. I'll take anyone.
Except the cleaning lady.
You owe me one.
I'll ride with Lieutenant Melon.
Damien's out of surgery.
but on life support.
It could go either way.
All right. so starting right
now. we treat this as a murder
case
because if this young man dies.
it will be.
Daphne. pull all security
footage from surrounding
buildings.
We need eyes on everyone
who was there that night.
You two go to the hospital.
See if this boy's family knows
anyone who might want him dead.
I'll be right there.
Hey. can I talk to you for a
second? -Of course.
So. when I agreed
to take this job--
I promised to look into your
missing ex. Um...
S... Roman Sinquerra.
Yeah. I'm assuming you might
need more than just his name.
You said he disappeared 15 years
ago. Can you tell me what
happened?
Yes. He went out to buy diapers
for Ava. my oldest. She was just
a baby back then.
He was driving a 1995 Mazda RX
- 7. California plates AAHQ729.
That's the last time I saw him.
Had you and Roman been--
Fighting? No. Listen.
I know what it sounds like.
like he went out for milk
and never came back.
It's a cliché for a reason.
That wasn't Roman.
All right. I'll see
what I can find.
Thank you.
You know what the best part of
my day has been so far?
Am I gonna be
flattered or offended?
Hopefully neither.
The best part of my day was
showing up to that crime scene
and not seeing a body
on top of that car.
Pretty sure I don't have to tell
you why. But now...
Now we don't know what
we're walking into.
You know. in this line of work.
Morgan. you have to hope for the
best
but be prepared for the worst.
It's your first day. so if you
wanna wait in the waiting room--
I'm good.
Okay.
Ms. Ross.
Please. call me Winnie.
Winnie. I'm Detective Karadec.
This is Morgan Gillory.
She's assisting me on your son's
case. We are so sorry about what
happened.
How's he doing?
The doctor said they don't know
if he'll survive the night.
And if he does. they don't know
if he'll walk again.
But growing up where he did.
he's beat the odds before.
He'll do it again.
I know this is a very difficult
time. Winnie.
We believe somebody pushed
Damien off that roof and. well.
I have to ask--
I know what you're gonna ask.
Detective. and the answer is no.
There is nobody in this world
who would wanna hurt my boy.
You know. on the way over here.
I had the opportunity to watch
your son tap. and it took my
breath away.
Your kid can really dance.
When Damien falls in
love with something. watch out.
Passionate and
stubborn. that one.
I wonder who he gets that from.
Damien has made his share of
mistakes before he started
working at BSB.
But they helped him
get his life together.
I'm sorry. I'm not
familiar with BSB.
Um. Body Shop Brothers.
It's a custom auto shop.
They hire at-risk youth and ex
- cons to fix up cars and get
their lives back on track.
Damien is saving the money he's
making from working at the shop
for a plane ticket to New York.
He's Broadway bound.
If he can just p-pull through
this time. if he can just...
Beat the odds again.
like you said.
Mama Ross?
Pardon me a moment.
I see two lefties.
And at least one catholic.
Not exactly a smoking gun.
- The phone was his.
- Whose?
The one who's got his
arm around Ms. Ross.
You see that elbow scar tattooed
over to look like baseball
stitching?
That's from a Tommy John injury.
From a torn ulnar ligament.
And he was a pitcher.
For De Perros de Tijuana.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm Detective Karadec.
Can we talk? It'll just take a
minute.
Mmm. Damien. Quite the talent.
He's next-level. no
question. Good-looking too.
So. Roland. how jealous
of him were you?
Jealous enough to
push him off a roof?
- I told you. I didn't push him.
- But you fought with him.
That's when you dropped your
phone. -No!
Damien and I never fought.
Check his coccyx!
Sounds like you have a
suggestion? -They gotta check
his coccyx.
I know this looks
really bad. but--
We have reason to believe
there's bruises and lacerations
on the suspect's backside.
We could get a warrant and make
you show us. or you could just
tell us.
Make the right choice
for us all. please.
You're right. we were
up there last night.
But Damien. he's
like a brother to me.
We met at the shop. When I told
him I used to dance. he offered
to teach me.
He helped me get my
life back together.
Then what happened on the roof?
Someone else pushed him.
Roland. do you actually expect
us to believe that?
I don't know
where the guy came from. okay?
He must have been
waiting there or something
because one minute we were
dancing and then...
he knocked me on my ass.
By the time I got up. Damien was
gone. him too. so I ran.
And let me guess. it was too
dark for you to see his face?
Without a witness
who actually saw Roland push
Damien.
we barely have
enough to hold him.
Daphne.
what about eyes in the sky?
Well. security camera across the
street showed Damien's car pull
in at 1:42 a.m.
- Any cameras in the alley?
- No. Got 'em everywhere else
though.
It's an old office building.
No occupants since last year.
Maybe squatters took up
residence in the building
and didn't like noise coming
from upstairs.
We checked.
They got this place locked down
tight.
No one going in or
out in the last week.
So either our third guy
teleported in and out. or he
doesn't exist.
He might.
What did you guys do
with Damien's car?
See I'm not the only one who
likes a little color on the
nails.
What have we got
here? Mushroom mimosa?
- Biscotti body. but close.
- Ooh.
Oh. boy.
Okay. I'm sorry. I'm not the one
who names nail polishes.
You've got three very patient
officers with you here in the
impound garage
and I can tell you that at least
one of them would like to know
the reason why.
Well. the reason why
is plasma chameleon paint.
See. plasma chameleon paint is
known for its color-changing
properties
because the pigment makes the
color change depending on the
angle and the lighting.
And that is why it is used
sometimes for nail polishes
and sometimes for custom paint
jobs for luxury cars.
Now. your lab... Well.
our lab found--
Our lab found traces of paint
in the trunk of the car.
which didn't surprise us
given that he does work
in an auto body shop
that paints cars.
But Damien loved
this baby so much.
there's no way he wasn't
vacuuming every square inch over
the weekends.
That is correct.
And since there's not a trace of
that paint on the outside of the
car.
and I highly doubt any of those
men hopped into the trunk
and painted his nails...
Anybody?
You think whoever pushed Damien
off the roof worked at the body
shop
and hid in the trunk of his car.
Yes. I do.
Roland was telling the truth.
There was a third man on the
roof
and that man hitched a ride
to the scene of his own crime.
That would explain why we didn't
see anyone arriving on the
scene.
The assailant got out of the car
in the alley and then followed
them up.
It's a good theory. Morgan. The
only problem is that this is an
'81 Regal.
The trunk release safety feature
wasn't introduced until the mid-
'80s.
which means if someone did sneak
in the trunk.
they wouldn't have been able to
get out. -I thought about that
too.
But what if one of
Damien's coworkers
decided to give him
a little unwanted trunk job.
Sounded grosser
than I wanted to.
Morgan. you are not helping.
- Close me in.
- I don't think that's a good
idea...
That was aggressive.
- This is getting weird now.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay. yeah. Give her a minute.
Yeah. there's no more minutes
for this. I'm...
Yep. found it.
Little rigged latch release
thingy.
Turns out. trunk job it is.
Looks like you and Morgan
have to go see the Body Shop
Brothers.
Am I helping now?
Detective Karadec.
Knox. right?
Chased you through Echo Park
a few years back.
What was it? Stolen property?
Identity theft?
Both.
What are you doing here.
Detective? -Just doing my job.
Now we have reason to believe
that the person who tried
to kill Damien works here too.
Detective.
if you're insinuating what I
think you're insinuating. we
don't appreciate that.
I'm not here
to earn your appreciation. Knox.
I'm here to find out who tried
to kill Damien.
Then go find him already.
I have an idea.
Uh. hear me out. What
if we did a trade?
Brought yourself a
random hot blonde. man?
I don't know about
random.
She's a consultant.
Let me handle this. please.
What kind of trade?
You guys tell us
where you were last night.
and we get Damien's car back
to the shop ASAP.
It's at impound.
That takes months.
What if it doesn't have to?
We're listening.
I bet Detective Karadec here
could call in a favor
and get Damien's car back
faster than he ran you down.
Knox.
Which isn't really
saying much. but...
Morgan. I actually... I can't
just-- -That way you guys will
have time
to fix up his car
and get it all ready for him
when he wakes up and comes home
from the hospital.
I didn't know the guy.
but I'm getting the sense
he would do the exact same thing
for you.
Damn right he would.
Excuse me.
Okay. Give me two
minutes with these guys.
For what?
Two minutes and I will get their
alibies right quick. right here
on the spot.
You promise?
Can you go just make a phone
call to see if you can get the
car?
Otherwise. we're not getting
anything out of them. you know
that.
Two minutes.
Okay.
Getting the sense that some
of you are very angry
about what happened to your
friend. Or numb. Heartbroken.
All very reasonable emotions
to have right now.
but wouldn't you guys feel
a little bit better
if you could help us find the
guy who hurt your friend?
You guys gotta tell me
where you were last night.
'Cause if you don't
tell me right now.
the cops are just gonna waste
time talking to other people.
like you.
who did absolutely nothing
wrong.
Go ahead. man.
Yeah. I guess I'll go first.
Okay.
First up is Dane.
Dane was on his fifth and.
hopefully. final date with Lola
last night.
The woman sounds
like a nightmare.
I hope he makes a good choice.
but he's young and stupid.
Then we got Big Bear Knox.
Knox was in Big Bear with his
dad.
They have a family cabin.
They go there pretty much weekly
to vamp it up a bit.
Fun perk of the job.
I did get an open invite to
visit.
Not a perk of the job.
Not for you.
Then we got Slappy.
Tall drink of water. handsome
fella.
Tough nut to crack.
but I tell you what--
Morgan. Is it safe to assume you
have this kind of info on all
these guys?
Yeah. That was the job.
- And where were you?
- Um...
So. Slappy was on
a date with his--
Uh. Morgan. hold up.
But I'm in the middle
of painting a picture.
You guys keep interrupting.
I have to say.
And I'm sure it's as stunning
as the Sistine Chapel.
but we really don't
have time for this.
Oh. I'm sorry. you don't have
time to give these gentlemen the
benefit of the doubt?
Did you all hear that?
Interesting. Is that because
they have a hard time with
authority? Who doesn't?
Lots of people.
Just download Daphne with the
details.
I'll make a case file to share
with a four-person team
that will track and trace the
movements of every suspect as
part of our ACP.
ACP?
Alibi Confirmation
Protocol. Come on.
Great.
She's a lot more fun than you.
All right.
- We got our work cut out for us.
- Mmm.
I wanna find out which one
of these Body Shop Bros
is our prime suspect by sunrise.
And since it turns out Roland
was telling the truth about the
third person...
I'll process his release.
Did you know that in 13th
- century Sweden. anyone could
put a thief to death? Anyone.
Say I caught Ava
swiping my Rubik's cube.
I could chop her head off
and it would just be like.
"Hold on. Why is the head
rolling around the floor?"
"Don't know.
I guess she must've stolen
something."
Ava. did you take
Elliot's Rubik's cube?
Yeah. Mom. I lust after
that Rubik's cube.
When are we getting
the car back?
I'm tired of leaving 45 minutes
early to take the bus.
As soon as I can afford
to get it out of the shop.
You've been saying that forever.
I know I have. Ava.
And every single time I have to
say it again. it kills me a
little more.
Ava got an A on her art project.
You did?
That's great. Why didn't you
tell me? Let me see it.
I think it shows
some real Cubist influence.
Look. It's Whiskers.
Buddy. that is really good.
It's okay.
Follow me.
What are you showing me?
This.
What are they?
They're murals painted
all over Los Angeles.
Aren't they great?
Yeah. they're pretty cool.
Your father painted those.
Awesome. Thanks for
showing me these.
Hey. You've been upset
that you didn't inherit my
talents.
but look. you got your dad's.
I got the talent of the guy
who walked out on us. Cool.
He did not walk out on us. Ava.
okay? I know it in my bones.
He just didn't do
it. He loved us.
And now I've got the full weight
of the LAPD looking into it.
We're gonna get to the truth.
How about they work
on getting our car back instead?
So. what? Just because you can't
sleep. I don't get to either?
Do you remember how
Damien's mom said
no one in the world
would wanna hurt her son?
Mm-hmm. Sometimes even moms
get it wrong. Morgan.
Maybe this time we
did. Let's dance.
- What are we doing?
- Come on.
Okay.
We thought the third man came up
onto the roof to kill Damien.
- And now you don't?
- Well. maybe.
But the best place for
the killer to hide.
where he wouldn't be seen by
the dancers. is over here
behind this structure.
So when Damien is close to the
edge. that is the killer's
moment.
He's got to move without
hesitation. He bolts forward.
He knocks over the tripod.
the cell phone goes flying.
All of which we already know.
Morgan. So what are we missing?
We forgot to look up.
Are you familiar
with the opposition effect?
Remind me.
The opposition effect
is an astronomical phenomenon
during the first and last
quarter phases of the moon
cycle.
That is when the moon is
at a 90-degree angle to the sun
and that's when it's
at its brightest.
And that happened last night?
Not only that. Roland called 911
at 2:14 a.m. Right?
So let's say he needed ten. 15
minutes to get down off the
roof.
get himself safe. pull himself
together and make a phone call.
Which would have placed
the time of impact shortly after
2:00.
Which places the
moon right there.
So. what do you
think the killer saw?
Roland and Damien
were in full shadow.
The moon was shining right
into the killer's eyes.
Moving fast under these
conditions. he couldn't see who
it was he was pushing.
Damien's mom was right.
No one wanted to kill her boy.
Our assailant pushed
the wrong guy.
He meant to kill Roland.
We released him from custody
a few hours ago.
If someone still wants him dead.
they can try again.
We gotta find Roland
before the killer does.
Yeah.
- Hey. momma.
- Hey. Everybody's okay back
there?
We're good. I already
put Chloe to bed.
And our son's Mandarin
is really coming along.
Though I guess I wouldn't know.
Yeah. Ava's okay?
She is still in her room.
She came out for some
ice cream.
and acknowledged me with a
grunt. which is reassuring.
Daphne just texted me Roland's
number and home address.
Ludo. I gotta go. I'm gonna be
later than I thought. I'm so
sorry.
- Yeah. Is everything okay?
- Yeah. No. I'm fine.
Don't worry about me. okay?
Thank you so much.
Mor-- Yeah. she's gone.
- Yeah?
- Roland. it's Detective Karadec.
- Who?
- Can you turn the music down. please?
- Not my call. bro.
- He's not at home.
It's Detective Karadec with the
LAPD. Roland. Where are you. buddy?
We need you to get someplace
safe.-What?
We believe you are in danger.
Sorry. man. Can't hear you.
This is Roland. Leave a
message.-
I'll have Daphne see
if she can locate him with a
trace.
I think he's at Gateway Towers.
- What?
- It's a warehouse that hosts
parties.
And you think he's there?
Yeah. I heard the song change
from Flip Fantasia to Culture
Beat.
so I googled '90s remix party
and the only one that came up
for tonight
- was at Gateway Towers.
- At Gateway Towers.
It's a little crime-fighting
tool called Google.
Might be a good time
to call for backup.
They're on the way.
but we don't have time to wait.
Okay. When Roland left the
precinct. he was wearing a green
hoodie.
black-and-white Adidas
Superstars. and a red Casio
watch.
Let's hope he didn't change.
Hey! Hey! Where's Roland?
- I don't know.
- Is he here?
Hey. what's going on?
They're looking for Roland.
How many times can you arrest a
guy in one day?
We're trying to help the young
man. Where is he?
I don't know. man. He was here.
I hadn't seen him in a minute.
Please help us find him.
Okay.
I'm going this way.
Excuse me.
God. Feel like I'm on the bus.
Roland!
- Hey! Roland!
- No. I'm John.
Nice to meet you.
John. Excuse me.
Yo. yo. He's over here.
Roland! Roland. come on. man.
We gotta get you outta here.
You...
You know. Morgan. what happened
tonight is just part of the job.
It's the worst part of the job.
I wish I could tell you it gets
easier. but it does not.
We didn't get here fast enough.
not tonight. but next time. we
will.
And when we do. I know we're
gonna have you to thank for it.
'Cause what you did on that roof
tonight. that was something.
I can't really take all the
credit for it. I had an assist.
Oh. yeah?
Yeah. my daughter Ava.
her dad's a painter.
Was a painter.
I don't know if he still paints.
I haven't seen him
in a long time. but...
He used to tell me that light
was the most important part of
the job.
Hey. guys.
Found something you're gonna
wanna see.
Hey. if this is too much for
you-- -No. I'm good. Let's find
this guy.
All those people
and nobody noticed a man being
shot?
Too loud. Plus all the lights.
The gunshot
was just one more flash in the
dark.
But if we look closer...
Looks like Roland
knew his killer.
And the killer knew everyone
there would have a phone on so
he hid his face.
And this is all we got?
Yeah. for now.
Any update on Damien?
Last we called the hospital.
it was still touch and go.
You okay?
Yeah. Well.
I'm just gonna take a little
walk.
There is nobody in this world
who would wanna hurt my boy.
In this line of work.
Morgan. you have to hope for
the best
but be prepared for the worst.
Yes?
Do you have this
on surveillance?
Uh... Yeah.
Play it.
Excuse me. What are
you doing?
Play the robbery.
Okay.
Oh. you take orders from her
now? This is highly
inappropriate.
Hang on. hang on.
Stop. Right there.
You see those sparks
after the muzzle flash?
The color and the trajectory.
That is a very old gun.
Now you're ammunitions expert.
I'm not. but I took my kids
to Pioneertown once.
and the gunsmith went on and on
about guns in the Wild West.
- What's going on?
- Come here. Look at these
sparks.
Okay. these sparks occur when
there is copper or lead left in
the barrel.
Usually. a very old
or poorly maintained gun.
and they cause a flash
like the one in this robbery
and in the one
that killed Roland.
So. great. Our robber is
at the O.K. Corral.
So you're saying you think that
his robber and our killer are
the same guy?
I'm saying same gun.
What do you think?
I think you should give her
some time with your board.
You serious? My board?
- Coming through. Thanks.
- Excuse us.
Eyes up.
Lieutenant Melon has
terrible handwriting.
Oh. the worst.
Hey. you really think his robber
is our killer?
I don't know.
But I know we gotta figure it
out.
Okay. so where do we start?
We start with why.
Why would this guy
wanna murder Roland?
You believe this?
The cleaning lady's
rearranging my boards.
You see a cleaning
lady. I see more.
Okay. sparkles. That's enough.
Morgan. what do you got?
I noticed something.
We've got five robberies. right?
The first three are
here. here and here.
And at each site.
an eyewitness saw the robber
get into a different getaway
car.
A red Camaro. a blue Mini...
An orange Corvette.
She gonna read
my entire case board back to me?
Now. at the fourth and fifth
site. there was no report of a
getaway car at all.
So. it's possible the driver
could've parked farther away?
Or something happened to the
car. -Or practice makes perfect.
They got faster and
no one saw him go.
What do you think?
I think the robber
lost his getaway car.
More importantly.
I think he lost his driver.
Now. see what these last two
jewelry stores have in common?
Okay. I'll give you a clue.
Now she's
drawing on my map.
Uh...
Really? Does no one
take public transit?
Okay. well. guess who does. This
guy. So let me walk you through
this.
This is the Red Line. Right here
are two stops along the Red
Line.
These are two jewelry stores
that are within one block of
those two stops.
You think the
robber was on foot?
Yes. I do.
And I think the missing getaway
driver. someone who had access
to multiple cars.
was Roland.
Think about it. He
worked at the shop.
Any of the cars that stayed
there overnight. he would've
had access to.
And the robber started hitting
stores on foot a month ago.
Right. That was
around the same time
that Damien helped Roland
escape a life of crime.
and they started posting
their dancing videos together.
That's right. so Roland tells
the robber. "I'm out."
But the robber can't trust
that Roland won't out him.
He knows that Damien and Roland
are dancing on rooftops all over
LA.
He decides to rig Damien's trunk
to push Roland off the roof.
But he pushes the wrong guy.
Now he's gotta find
Roland at the club.
And to make sure
he does it right this time.
he brings his gun.
Look. this is great police work.
Morgan. but do you know who this
guy is?
No. I don't.
But I do have an idea
about how we can find him.
All units 6837. we have
a 187. Respond code 3.
Repeat. all units 6837. we have
Hands in the air!
Nobody move! -LAPD! Put your
hands up!
- Drop your weapon!
- LAPD!
Put the gun on the ground
slowly. Lay down on the floor.
Belly on the floor now. Down.
Hands behind your back.
Let's go.
He looks confused.
- Are you confused. Griff?
- Lawyer.
You don't wanna talk. I get it.
You don't have to.
But I bet you're wondering how
we knew you'd be here.
- Can I tell him?
- Tell him.
See. I think you really were
upset about what happened to
Damien.
The red eyes. the tears.
those were real 'cause you
didnt't mean to hurt him.
But you see. mixed in with that
sadness. I saw something else:
guilt.
Oh. side note. contrition
gonna be helpful for you
when you're talking
to the parole board
after you're convicted
of murdering Roland.
So. how did we manage to show up
and spoil your party?
Well. joke's on you. it's our
party. bud. and we invited you.
Because we noticed that every
time you would rob a jewelry
store.
it would happen right after a
code 3 went out on the police
scanner.
You figured the fewer
units available.
the likelier chance you'd have
to be able to get away.
But. luckily for the residents
of Los Angeles.
there's no actual code 3
happening tonight.
Just a 211. yours.
Let's go.
Heard a little rumor. Somebody
just closed their first official
case with the LAPD.
So I did help.
You had your moments. which is
why Soto asked me to give you
this.
First official
paycheck. Lands early.
No way.
Oh.
Wow.
Karadec.
Yeah. Got it.
That was the hospital.
Damien's awake.
Please come on in.
- Hi.
- There's somebody I want you to
meet.
These are the people I told you
were trying to figure out what
happened.
Thank you.
- Damien moved his toes today.
- No way.
The doctors believe with some
work. he'll be dancing in no
time.
That's right.
You know. because of you. I was
able to find out this guy's
never seen a tap show.
What? You got something
against a good time?
- No. no. I love a good time.
- Mmm.
Then one day I'll get you some
tickets. Both of you.
Least I could do.
I heard about Roland and Griff.
It's over now
though. Don't worry.
Nah. I'm just getting started.
Now. what the hell are y'all
still doing here?
Get your ass. get back to the
shop and fix my car. Now.
- Okay.
- Oh. gosh.
That's what I said.
for the record.
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- Take care.
I need some wheels.
You know. that's not too bad
for your first case. Gillory.
I'm just glad I was able to
help. -Mm-hmm.
Have you thought about quitting
while you're ahead. you know?
Kinda go out on top.
You do not want me to quit.
You're having way too much fun.
- Oh. I am. huh?
- Yep.
Like driving you all over town.
No. No. that does have to stop.
♪ Oh. this time ♪
♪ This time. I know I'm
fighting♪ -
♪ This time. I know I'm ♪
♪ This time. I
know I'm fighting ♪
No way!
♪ This time. I know I'm ♪
♪ Lost you in the border town
Of anywhere ♪
♪ I found myself
When I was going everywhere ♪
♪ This time. I
know I'm fighting ♪
♪ This time. I know I'm ♪
♪ And all along the highway ♪
♪ There's a tiny whispering
sound♪ -
♪ Saying I could find you
In the dark of any town ♪
I'm so sorry to
just pop by. Morgan.
You're firing me
in the comfort of my own home?
That's a classy
move. I respect that.
- You wanna come in?
- No. no. that's okay. I had some
news.
You were on my way home.
I thought you'd wanna hear it.
- What is it?
- I followed up on Roman's car.
Turns out it ended up in police
impound three days after he
disappeared.
It was abandoned in
a Costco parking lot
a couple of miles
from where you both lived.
In the short inventory of items
discovered in the car was a box
of diapers.
which of course
begs the question.
if Roman really wanted
to abandon your family.
why would he stop and
buy diapers first?
You believe me.
We're gonna find out what
happened to Roman.
I promise.
Thank you.
♪ I found myself
When I was going everywhere ♪
♪ This time. I
know I'm fighting ♪
♪ This time. I know
I'm back in my body. oh ♪
♪ I'm back in my body. oh ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm